KAVYA RAJSB

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

8921262775

kavyarajkavz2000@gmail.com

Thiruvananthapuram, Kerala

https://www.linkedin.com/in/kavya-raj-s-b-a45b3a17b

PROFILE

An IT professional experienced in UI/UX with ability to translate business requirements into technical solutions. Proficient in MEAN stack & PERN stack technologies and currently working as a Junior Technology Innovator – R&D

PORTFOLIO: https://kavyarajsb.github.io/Portfolio/

EXPERIENCE

Ciber Digita Consultants Ilp. (Mar 2023- Present)

Junior Technology Innovator – R&D

- ReactJS with css frameworks like React-bootstrap, Ant Design & Material UI
- State management with Redux and Redux-saga
- PostgreSQL, and handling asynchronous requests with Axios
- ExpressJS and NodeJS for server-side development
- Docker
- JSON & ECMAScript

TCS iON (Jan 2023- Feb 2023)

MEAN Stack Intern

- HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- Frontend frameworks- Angular with css frameworks like Bootstap, Angular material
- MongoDB
- ExpressJS and NodeJS for server-side development
- Experienced in version control systems like **GitHub and Git**, and deployment platforms like **Heroku & Cyclic**
- Proficient in Adobe Photoshop for graphic design and logo creation, as well as
 Microsoft Office for productivity tasks

EDUCATION

- FULL STACK DEVELOPMENT (July 2022- Dec 2022)
 - -ICT Academy of Kerala, TVM
- GRADUATE IN CIVIL ENGINEERING (2017-2021)
 - -Mohandas college of Engineering & Technology ,Anad, Nedumangadu, TVM CGPA- 8.64
- HIGHER SECONDARY- BIOLOGY SCIENCE (2015-2017)
 - -Govt. H S S Bharathannoor Percentage- 92.75%
- SSLC (2015)
 - -Govt. H S S Bharathannoor Percentage-95%

PROJECTS

- https://github.com/Kavyarajsb?tab=repositories
- Shopping Cart (ReactJS, Redux, Redux-saga, PostrgeSQL, NodeJS, ExpressJS)
- Content Management System (Angular, MongoDB, NodeJS, ExpressJS)

Video Link of work: https://www.loom.com/share/ae08809a08e74be3b623fae0349cbbbc

ICTAK Learner Tracker Website (Angular, MongoDB, NodeJS, ExpressJS)

Hosted Link: https://cheerful-ox-threads.cyclic.app/

- Library App (Angular, MongoDB, NodeJS, ExpressJS)
- To-Do App(ReactJS, PostrgeSQL, NodeJS, ExpressJS)
- Kerala Tourism Website (HTML, CSS & Javascript)

Hosted Link: https://kavyarajsb.github.io/Kerala_Tourism_website_Homepage/

PERSONAL INFORMATION

• Gender: Female

Father: Baburajan D

• DOB: 1st January 2000

· Marital status: unmarried

LANGUAGES

- English
- Malayalam (Native)
- Hindi

I hereby declare that all the informations furnished above is true to best of my belief.